Guide to the Franklin Bowditch Dexter Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Files on Alumni, Circa 1701-1912; Series I; 9' (22 boxes)
  - Goode, William Henry. 1842m (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Goodhart, Morris. 1867l (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Goodhue, Jonathan Elbridge. 1852 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Goodhue, Josiah Cosmore. 1829m (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Goodhue, William Sewall. 1818m (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Goodrich, Charles. 1797 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Goodrich, Charles Rush. 1849 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey Allen. 1810 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Goodrich, Hezekiah. 1788 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Goodrich, Horace. 1814 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Goodrich, Joseph. 1821 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Goodwin, Edward. 1823 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Goodyear, Watson Andrews. 1863p (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Gordon, Edwin Everett. 1842m (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Gordon, George Anderson. 1849
    See: Dimmick, Alpheus, box 6, folder 54.
  - Gordon, George William. 1851 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Gordon, John Montgomery. 1830 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Gordon, Wellington. 1831 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Gormly, Edwin Curtis. 1866
    See: Poole, Benjamin, box 14, folder 160.
  - Gould, Archibald Falconer. 1852h (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Gould, Horace Bunch. 1832
  - Gould, William Tracy. 1816
  - Goulding, John. 1821 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Gower, Henry Lee. 1880 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Gradey, William Postell. 1842 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Graham, John. 1737h (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Graham, John. 1740 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Graham, John Augustus. 1768 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Grammer, John. 1817
    See: box 20, folder 243.
  - Grant, Elijah Phelps. 1830 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Grant, Joel. 1838 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Grant, John. 1845 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Grary, Thomas. 1815 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Graves, HorationNelson. 1826 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Graves, Starling. 1765 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Gray, Ebenezer. 1805 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Green, Richard Henry. 1857 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Greene, David. 1821 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Greene, Edward Wing. 1826m (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Greene, George Nelson. 1860 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Greene, Leonard Vassall. 1878p (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Greene, Ray. 1784 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Greene, William Brooks. 1845 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Gregorii, Thomas Hutson. 1828 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Gregory, Elijah. 1856m (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Gregory, Ira. 1829m (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Gridley, Elihu. 1787 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Gridley, Elijah. 1784 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Gridley, Elnathan. 1819 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Gridley, Frederick. 1816 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Gridley, Horatio. 1815 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Gridley, Timothy Jones. 1808 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Griffin, Edward Dorr. 1790
    See: Williams, Joseph, box 19, folder 224.
  - Grimball, Paul Chaplin. 1810 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Griswold, Charles Woodford. 1871p (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Griswold, George William. 1816 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Griswold, Roger Wolcott. 1818 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Griswold, Samuel. 1818 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Griswold, Stanley. 1786
    See: Stanley, Henry, box 16, folder 190.
  - Grosvenor, Thomas Peabody. 1800 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Grout, Alfred. 1853 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Grove, Peter Houtz. 1867p (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Groves, LaFayette Washington. 1855 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Guernsey, Charles Whittlesey. 1875d (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Guilford, Nathan. 1812
    See:box 20, folder 243.
  - Gunn, Alexander Hunter. 1854 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Gunn, Frederick. 1810
  - Gunn, Frederick William. 1837 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Gunn, Moses. 1748 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Gunton, William Alexander. 1847 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Gurley, John Ward. 1799h (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hadley, James. 1842 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Haldeman, Richard Jacobs. 1851 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hale, Albert. 1827 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hale, Eden Thomas. 1862 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hale, Elizur. 1742 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hale, Enoch. 1773 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hale, Nathan. 1774
    See: Williams, Elisha Scott, box 19, folder 223.
  - Hall, Aaron. 1772 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hall, Amos Potter. 1807 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hall, Asaph. 1879h (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hall, Benjamin. 1754 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hall, David Ebenezer. 1820m (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hall, Edwin. 1850 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hall, Eli. 1830 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hall, Elisha. 1764 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hall, Franklin Wilson. 1877m (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hall, George. 1803 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Hall, Henry Lewis. 1860 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Hall, Jonathan. 1736 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Hall, Jonathan Prescott. 1817 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Hall, Lee. 1789 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Hall, Levi Wells. 1866h (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Hall, Lyman. 1747 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Hall, Newton Bushnell. 1863m (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Hall, Philip. 1815m (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Hall, Prince Briant. 1788 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Hall, Richard. 1750 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Hall, Samuel Birch. 1837 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Hall, William Charles James. 1851 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Hallam, Amos. 1756 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Hallock, Minor. 1814 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Hallock, Moses. 1788
    See: Payne, Elisha, box 13, folder 151.
  - Hamelin, John Lawrence. 1840 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Hamilton, Frederick William. 1823 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Hamilton, William Abbott. 1868 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Hamlin, Alanson. 1799 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Hammond, Asa. 1814 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Hammond, Edward. 1830 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Hammond, George Charles Wilcox. 1848l (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Hampton, John Preston. 1804 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Hand, Chauncey Meigs. 1850 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Hand, George Edward. 1829 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Hand, George Edward. 1869 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Hanford, Frederick Augustus. 1830 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Hard, David Brinsmade Wilcockson. 1834m (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Hardyear, Jabez G. 1818m (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Hareston, Edward. 1815 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Harmon, John Brown. 1842h (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Harper, John Randolph. 1848 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Harper, Samuel Henderson. 1831h (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Harper, William Riddle. 1845 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Harrington, George Dana. 1845 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Harrington, Joseph. 1803 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Harris, Henry Reeder. 1836 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Harris, William Torrey. 1858 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Harrison, Benjamin Franklin. 1836m
  - Harrison, George Torrence. 1869 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Harrison, Hugh Thompson. 1831 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Harrison, James. 1836 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Harrison, Jared. 1736 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Harrison, Roger. 1791 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Hart, Augustine. 1853 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Hart, David Sherman. 1823m (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Hart, John. 1776 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Hart, John Clark. 1831 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Hart, Levi. 1760 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Hart, Roswell. 1843 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Hart, Rufus Erastus. 1833 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Hart, Seth. 1784 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Hart, William. 1792 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Hart, William Backus. 1817 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Hartshorn, Isaac. 1828 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    See also: Udall, Richard Athill, box 17, folder 208.
  - Hartwell, Moses. 1762 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Hartwell, Samuel Slawson. 1859 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    See also: Wickham, William, box 18, folder 221.
  - Harvey, Joseph. 1808 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    See also: Vaill, Herman Landon, box 21, folder 257.
  - Hasbrouck, Abraham Bruyn. 1810
  - Hasbrouck, Jansen. 1831 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Hasell, William Soranzo. 1799 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Haskell, Ezra. 1811 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Haskell, Willabe. 1863 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Hastings, George Granbery. 1851 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Hastings, John. 1815 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Hatch, Moses. 1800 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Hatch, Roger Conant. 1815 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Hathaway, Joshua. 1787 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Hathaway, Shadrach. 1738
    See:box 20, folder 244.
  - Haughee, Thomas. 1864 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Haughton, Richard. 1818 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Havens, Charles Horace. 1806
    See: Hallock, Minor, box 8, folder 84.
  - Havens, Daniel William. 1843 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Hawes, Lowman. 1814 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Hawes, Wells. 1834 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Hawkins, Alexander Thomas. 1826 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Hawks, Winthrop Butler. 1882d (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Hawley, Almon. 1829m (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Hawley, Charles. 1813 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Hawley, Charles DeForest. 1876 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Hawley, Isaac. 1817 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Hawley, James Augustus. 1837 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Hawley, Roswell. 1842m (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Haxall, Robert William. 1823 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Hayden, William Hallock. 1847 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Hayes, Charles Gordon. 1851 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Hayes, Gordon. 1823 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Hayes, Samuel. 1823 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Hayes, William Rutherford. 1825 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Haywood, Elisha. 1820 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Hazelton, Silas. 1779 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Hazen, James Alexander. 1834 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Hazen, Reuben Stedman. 1818 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Heart, Jonathan. 1768 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Heath, Peleg. 1721 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Heaton, Benjamin Kaye. 1885 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Heaton, Samuel. 1728 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Hebard, Albert. 1851
    See: Smith, Moses, box 16, folder 187.
  - Hebard, Alfred. 1832 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Hebard, Daniel. 1860
    See: box 20, folder 244.
  - Hecock, Simeon. 1802 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Hedges, David Anson. 1857m (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Hedges, Edwin. 1869 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Hedges, Jeremiah. 1764 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Hegeman, George Stewart. 1878p (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Hemenway, Daniel Egerton. 1862 non-graduate (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Heminway, Jacob. 1704 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Hennen, Alfred. 1806 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Hennen, William Davison. 1842 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Henry, Thomas Carlton. 1824h (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Henson, Rufus Alexander. 1849 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Hequembourg, Charles Lewis. 1835 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Herrick, Edward. 1796
  - Herrick, Edward Claudius. 1838h
  - Hewitt, Nathaniel. 1808
  - Hickock, Lyman. 1806
    See: Hecock, Simeon, box 9, folder 91.
  - Hickok, Horatio. 1798
  - Hickok, James W. 1840l non-graduate (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Hickok, Norman. 1803 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Higbie, Daniel. 1836 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Higginson, Louis Maynard. 1880p (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Hill, Charles Borland. 1861 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Hill, Cyrus Foss. 1881 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Hill, Joshua. 1835 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Hill, Whitmill John. 1823 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Hillyer, Samuel Lee. 1875d (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Hinckley, Edward Strong. 1859
  - Hinckley, George. 1810 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Hincks, John Howard. 1872 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hincks, William Bliss. 1878h (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hine, Homer. 1797 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hini, Jeremiah. 1815 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hinman, Royal Ralph. 1804 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hinsdale, Charles James. 1815 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hinsdale, Theodore. 1821 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hitchcock, Daniel. 1761 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hitchcock, Henry Lawrence. 1832 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hitchcock, Samuel Johnson. 1809 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    See also: Staples, Job, box 21, folder 255.
  - Hite, Levi. 1875l (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hobby, Loamm, Ives. 1817 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hoagland, Christopher Colombus. 1832m (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hobby, Alfred McKinne. 1814 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hodges, Henry Kelley. 1858p (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hodges, Willard. 1845 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Hoffman, George. 1863 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Hoffman, George Brice. 1828
    See: box 20, folder 245.
  - Hoffman, Murray. 1842 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Hoffman, Philip Rogers. 1827 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Hogeboom, Henry. 1827 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Holbrook, Samuel. 1801
  - Holcombe, Gustavus Adolphus. 1840 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Holden, Edward. 1812 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Holley, Nathaniel. 1795 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Holley, Platt Taylor. 1828 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Hollister, Gideon Hiram. 1840 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Hollister, Shelton. 1848 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Holman, George Payne. 1831 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Holmes, Franklin. 1846 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Holmes, Isaac Edward. 1815 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Holmes, Stephen. 1752 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Holmes, Uriel. 1784 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Holt, Eleazar. 1823 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Holt, Hiram. 1834h (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Honeywood, St. John. 1732 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Hooker, George. 1814 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Hooker, John. 1810 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Hopkins, Arthur Moseley. 1836 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Hopkins, Charles. 1855h
  - Hopkins, Samuel Miles. 1791
    See: Ver Plank, William Gordon, box 18, folder 210.
  - Hopkins, William Fenn. 1831h (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Hopson, John. 1757 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Horton, Henry. 1854 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Horton, William Walter. 1846 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Hosley, Simon D. 1821, 1829 non-graduate
    See: Train, Elijah Nickerson, box 17, folder 204.
  - Hosmer, Stephen. 1732 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Hotchkins, Hermon Jackson. 1822m (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Hotchkiss, Caleb. 1766
  - Hotchkiss, Gabriel. 1774
  - Hough, Alanson Hodges. 1832m (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Hough, John. 1802 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Houghton, Ephraim. 1816m (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Houghton, Israel. 1767 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Houstoun, Robert James. 1805 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Howard, Horace Cobb. 1877p (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Howard, Jonathan Jones. 1851m (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Howard, Joshua. 1763 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Howard, Virgil Maro. 1851 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Howarth, Wilbur Griswold. 1865l (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Howe, Eleazar Williams. 1776 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Howe, James Hervey. 1835 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Howe, Samuel. 1827 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Howe, William Henry. 1847 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Howell, George Rogers. 1854 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Howell, John. 1721 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Howes, Abraham Lincoln. 1886h
    See: DeWolf, Carlton Melville, box 6, folder 52.
  - Hoyt, John Benedict. 1814 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Hoyt, Joseph Gibson. 1840 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Hoyt, Melancthon. 1830 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Hubbard, Anson. 1817 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, Austin Osgood. 1824 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, Bela. 1792 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, Chauncey Henry. 1840 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, Daniel. 1727 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, Daniel Green. 1852 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, Denison Hale. 1829m (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, George. 1835m (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, Henry. 1792 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, Jabez Brooks. 1825 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, Jonathan. 1724 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, John. 1744 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, John Parkinson. 1848 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, Lucius. 1788 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, Oliver Payson. 1828 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbard, Ruggles. 1796 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    See also: Gale, Benjamin, box 8, folder 72.
  - Hubbard, Thomas Robinson. 1829 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Hubbell, Horatio. 1818 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Hudson, William Wilson. 1827 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Huggins, Zenas. 1757 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Hull, Aretius Bevil. 1807 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Hull, Charles Perry. 1879p (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Humphrey, Charles Edward. 1874 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Humphrey, Philander Phelps. 1848m (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Humphreys, David. 1771 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Hungerford, Allyn Merriam. 1839m (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Hunn, David Lathrop. 1813 (Box 10, Folder 99)
    See also:Withington, Leonard, box 19, folder 227.
  - Hunt, Isaac Shafer. 1847m
  - Hunt, Seth. 1768 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Hunt, William Henry. 1878h (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Huntington, Andrew. 1815 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Huntington, Dan. 1794 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Huntington, Elisha. 1823m (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Huntington, Enoch. 1785 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Huntington, Jedidiah. 1814 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Huntington, Nathaniel. 1747 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Huntington, Norman Spencer. 1840 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Huntting, James Murdock. 1824
    See: box 20, folder 246.
  - Huntting, Samuel. 1767 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Hurd, John Codman. 1836 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Hurd, Theodore Canfield. 1830m (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Hurlbut, Salmon. 1763 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Hurlbutt, August Moën. 1876
    See: Trowbridge, William Henry, box 17, folder 205.
  - Hurlbutt, Lewis Raymond. 1843
  - Husted, Hiram Wildman. 1823 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Huston, Seth Craige. 1831 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Hutchins, James Howard. 1840m (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Hutchinson, Aaron. 1747 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Hutchinson, Morison Thomas. 1886p (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Hyatt, Robert Underwood. 1837 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Hyde, Dougal Cameron. 1847l (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Hyde, James Thomas. 1847 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Hyde, Oren. 1820h (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Ingersoll, Daniel Wesley. 1866 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Ingersoll, David Bryan. 1792 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Ingersoll, John Jarvis. 1814 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Ingersoll, Ralph Isaacs. 1808 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Ingersoll, William Fletcher. 1858 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Irving, John Beaufain. 1823m (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Isaacs, Benjamin. 1781 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Isham, John Beach. 1869 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Isham, Joseph Henry. 1865 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Isham, Lucius Dwight. 1849m (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Isham, Oliver Kingsley. 1822m (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Ives, Ansel W. 1821h (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Ives, George Whitfield. 1841 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Ives, Homer DeGrasse. 1843l (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Ives, Isaac. 1785 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Ives, Joseph. 1782 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Ives, Matthew. 1824 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Ives, Nathaniel. 1819m (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Ives, Thomas. 1777
    See: Tuthill, Samuel, box 17, folder 206.
  - Ives, Wilbur. 1863 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Jack, Thomas McKinney. 1853 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Jackson, Angelo. 1847 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Jackson, John. 1844 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Jackson, William Alfred. 1883 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Jacob, Stephen. 1778
  - Jacobs, Benjamin Willard. 1889 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - James, Lorenzo. 1825
  - James, Thomas D. 1845h (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Jamison, Blain. 1881p (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Jarvis, Abraham. 1761 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Jarvis, Samuel Farmer. 1805
  - Jay, William. 1807 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Jennings, George Conkling. 1883 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Jennings, Gould J. 1854l (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Jennings, Isaac. 1828h (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Jessup, William. 1815 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Jesup, Ebenezer. 1760 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    See also: Andrews, Ebenezer, box 1, folder 3.
  - Jesup, Ebenezer. 1824 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Jewett, John. 1879P (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Jocelin, Samuel Russell. 1783 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johns, Evan. 1809h (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johnson, Abner. 1759 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johnson, Barclay. 1882 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johnson, Caleb. 1785 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johnson, Charles Napolean. 1858 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johnson, Edward Whiting. 1869p
  - Johnson, Henry Clay. 1884p (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johnson, Jacob. 1740 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johnson, James, (1760) (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johnson, James Derham. 1813 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johnson, Joshua. 1775 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johnson, Robert Charles. 1783 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johnson, Samuel. 1714 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johnson, Samuel. 1829 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Johnston, Alexander. 1843 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Johnston, William Patrick. 1833 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Jones, Charles. 1843 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Jones, George. 1823 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Jones, George Noble. 1829 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Jones, Harding. 1756 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Jones, Isaac. 1742
    See: box 21, folder 247.
  - Jones, Isaac. 1757
  - Jones, Isaac. 1792
  - Jones, James Stone. 1872 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Jones, Joel. 1817 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Jones, John. 1776 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Jones, John Nelson. 1818 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Jones, John Thomas. 1808 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Jones, Samuel. 1790 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Jones, Samuel. 1800 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Jones, Samuel Beach. 1831
  - Jones, Stephen Farrar. 1812 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Jones, William. 1762
    See: Jones, Isaac (1742), box 21, folder 247.
  - Jones, William Hemphill. 1831
  - Jones, William Henry 1796 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    See also: Talcott, Thomas Grosvenor, box 17, folder 198.
  - Judd, Jonathan. 1820h (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Judd, Timothy. 1737 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    See also: Camp, Joseph Eleazor, box 4, folder 31.
  - Judson, Albert. 1821 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Judson, David. 1775 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Judson, David. 1778 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Judson, David Plant. 1831 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Judson, Isaac Edwards. 1803 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Judson, Philander. 1800 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Judson, Philo. 1809 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Judson, William. 1834 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Kanouse, Peter. 1831h
  - Keep, Theodore John. 1832 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Keese, Sidmon Thorne. 1860 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Kellogg, Alfred. 1818 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Kellogg, Ebenezer. 1757 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    See also: Talcott, Joel, box 17, folder 197.
    See also: Wright, Ebenezer, box 19, folder 233.
  - Kellogg, Ezra. 1807 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Kellogg, Gardiner. 1791 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Kellogg, Giles Crouch. 1800 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Kellogg, Jonathan Warren. 1803 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Kellogg, Joseph. 1763 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Kelsey, Aaron Hervey. 1805 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Kelsey, Eli. 1788 deceased in senior year (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Kennedy, Archibald. 1846 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Kenyon, William Henry. 18711 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Kerr, Elias Loffborough. 1864 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Kerr, Samuel Chamberlain. 1833 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Keteltas, Philip Doddridge. 1792
  - Key, Thomas Marshall. 1838 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Keyes, Henry Plumer. 1842 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Keyes, Stephen. 1773 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Keyes, Winfield Scott. 1860 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Kibbe, Walter Raleigh. 1804 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Kidder, Joseph. 1764 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Kilbourn, James. 1837 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Kilbourn, John. 1840 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Kimball, David. 1818 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Kimball, Timothy. 1774 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Kimberly, William Russell. 1862 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Kimpton, Hiram Hollister. 1862 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - King, Asa Howe. 1821 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - King, Nathaniel. 1792 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Kingsbury, Ebenezer. 1783 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Kingsbury, Jonathan. 1767 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Kingsbury, Sanford. 1763 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Kingsland, Thorn Sell. 1823 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Kinkead, Milton. 1859l (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Kinne, Aaron. 1794 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Kinne, William. 1804 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Kissam, Daniel. 1810 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Knapp, Jared Owen. 1840 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Knapp, Samuel Trevor. 1872p (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Kneeland, Ebenezer. 1761 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Knight, Isaac. 1767 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Knox, Hugh. 1800 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Knox, John Reynolds. 1822 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Kollock, George Jones. 1829 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Krusi, Herman. 1872h (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Lacey, Noah A. 1824h (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Laisum, Elijah Thien Foh. 1877p (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Lake, Wells Cushman. 1875p (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Lamb, David. 1840 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Lamb, Joseph. 1717